let data = {
    quizData: [
        {
            id: "0",
            question: "Which is the most widely spoken language in the world?",
            options: ["Spanish", "Mandarin", "English", "German"],
            correct: "Mandarin",
        },
        {
            id: "1",
            question: "Which is the only continent in the world without a desert?",
            options: ["North America", "Asia", "Africa", "Europe"],
            correct: "Europe",
        },
        {
            id: "2",
            question: "Who invented Computer?",
            options: ["Charles Babbage", "Henry Luce", "Henry Babbage", "Charles Luce"],
            correct: "Charles Babbage",
        },
        {
            id: "3",
            question: "Alongside former President Frederik Willem de Klerk, which then President of South Africa won a Nobel prize for their work to peacefully end apartheid in the country?",

            options: ["Mgabe", "Henry Gbague", "Nelson Mandela", "Luke Mooore"],
            correct: "Nelson Mandela",
        },
        {
            id: "4",
            question: "How many cards are there in a pack of cards (not incl. jokers)?",
            options: ["52", "53", "50", "32"],
            correct: "52",
        },
        {
            id: "5",
            question: "What does www stand for?",
            options: ["World wide web", "West Wide World", "Wide wide west", "Web Wide World"],
            correct: "World wide web",
        },
        {
            id: "6",
            question: "Where might you find Tower Bridge and Buckingham Palace, amongst many other landmarks?",
            options: ["Canada", "London", "Paris", "USA"],
            correct: "London",
        },
        {
            id: "7",
            question: "What is the name of Mickey Mouse’s partner?",
            options: ["Minnie Mouse", "Mouse", "Nicky Mouse", "Nicky"],
            correct: "Minnie Mouse",
        },
        {
            id: "8",
            question: "What country is famous for inventing the Taco, Burrito and Quesadilla?",
            options: ["Italy", "Spain", "Mexico", "France"],
            correct: "Mexico",
        },
        {
            id: "9",
            question: "Who is the South African born CEO of SpaceX and the brains behind Tesla?",
            options: ["Mark Zukerberg", "Elon Musk", "Jeff Bezos", "Ma"],
            correct: "Elon Musk",
        },
        {
            id: "10",
            question: "What animal is Pumbaa in the Lion King?",
            options: ["A Lion", "A Zebra", "A Lioness", "A warthog"],
            correct: "A warthog",
        },
        {
            id: "11",
            question: "What company is responsible for the iPhone, iPad and iWatch and many other products?",
            options: ["Apple", "Andriod", "HTC", "XOS"],
            correct: "Apple",
        },
        {
            id: "12",
            question: "What is the largest country by area in the world?",
            options: ["Russia", "USA", "India", "China"],
            correct: "Russia",
        },
        {
            id: "13",
            question: "In which country would you find Angel Falls, the highest waterfall on earth?",
            options: ["Cameroon", "Venezuela", "South Africa", "Columbia"],
            correct: "Venezuela",
        },
        {
            id: "14",
            question: "What city is the capital of France?",
            options: ["Lyon", "Troyes", "Paris", "Lile"],
            correct: "Paris",
        },
        {
            id: "15",
            question: "How many states are there in America? ",
            options: ["49", "50", "51", "52"],
            correct: "50",
        },
        {
            id: "16",
            question: "Name the capital of China.",
            options: ["Beijing", "Chou Zhoua", "Goan", "Lie jung"],
            correct: "Beijing",
        },
        {
            id: "17",
            question: "Which is larger the Pacific or the Atlantic Ocean?",
            options: ["Pacific", "Atlantic Ocean", "None", "Both"],
            correct: "Pacific",
        },
        {
            id: "18",
            question: "Who was assassinated, leading to the start of the First World War?",
            options: ["Granz Murphy", "Archduke Franz Ferdinand", "Duke Ferdinando", "Adolf Hitler"],
            correct: "Archduke Franz Ferdinand",
        },
        {
            id: "19",
            question: "Who conquered England in 1066?",
            options: ["William (the Conqueror)", "James (the Conqueror)", "Jacob (the Conqueror)", "Harry (the Conqueror)"],
            correct: "William (the Conqueror)",
        },
        {
            id: "20",
            question: "In what year did the US sign the declaration of Independence, now celebrated on 4th July each year?",
            options: ["1776", "1786", "1796", "1806"],
            correct: "1776",
        },
        {
            id: "21",
            question: "Where was the famous attack by Japan that led to America joining World War II?",
            options: ["Pearl Harbor", "Duke Harlum", "David West", "Jack Zukhi"],
            correct: "Pearl Harbor",
        },
        {
            id: "22",
            question: "Which British King famously had six wives?",
            options: ["Henry VIII", "Harry VIII", "Ryan VIII", "Justin VIII"],
            correct: "Henry VIII",
        },
        {
            id: "23",
            question: "In which city was Jesus said to have been born?",
            options: ["Bneiu Yehuda", "Cairo", "Jarusalem", "Bethlehem"],
            correct: "Bethlehem",
        },
        {
            id: "24",
            question: "What is the most played sport in India and has produced many greats of the game including Sachin Tendulkar and Sunil Gavaskar?",
            options: ["Cricket", "Soccer", "Tennis", "Dancing"],
            correct: "Cricket",
        },
        {
            id: "25",
            question: "The All Blacks are the rugby team of which country?",
            options: ["USA", "London", "France", "New Zealand"],
            correct: "New Zealand",
        },
        {
            id: "26",
            question: "Which English footballer retired in 2006 with a record 260 Premiership goals?",
            options: ["Wayne Rooney", "Ryan Gigs", "Alan Shearer", "Fletcher"],
            correct: "Alan Shearer",
        },
        {
            id: "27",
            question: "Which basketball team became the first to reach the milestone of 3,000 wins in 2010?",
            options: ["Chicago Bulls", "LA Lakers", "NY Bulls", "Eagles"],
            correct: "LA Lakers",
        },
        {
            id: "28",
            question: "Dubbed the ‘King of Pop’, which artist released the album Thriller, which went on to be the bestselling album of all time?",
            options: ["Prince", "Michael Jackson", "Madonna", "Witney Huston"],
            correct: "Michael Jackson",
        },
        {
            id: "29",
            question: "Which famous US singer was born in Tupelo, Mississippi in 1935 and died aged in 1977 in Graceland, Tennessee?",
            options: ["Elvis", "Prince", "Andre", "James Brown"],
            correct: "Elvis",
        },

        {
            id: "30",
            question: "What is the name of the royal singer who turned the rain purple?",
            options: ["James Brown", "Prince", "Elvis", "Michael Jackson"],
            correct: "Prince",
        },
        {
            id: "31",
            question: "La Louvre and Musee D’Orsay are famous museums in which city?",
            options: ["Paris", "Lile", "Rome", "Eibar"],
            correct: "Paris",
        },
        {
            id: "32",
            question: "Acquired by Disney from this famous George for $4 billion in 2012, was which film production house? ",
            options: ["Lucasfilm", "justfilm", "thrillerfilm", "johnfilm"],
            correct: "Lucasfilm",
        },
        {
            id: "33",
            question: "In beer, what does IPA stand for?",
            options: ["Indian Pale All", "Indian Pale Ale", "Ideal Pale Ale", "Indian Part Ale"],
            correct: "Indian Pale Ale",
        },
        {
            id: "34",
            question: "Vanilla is native to which country?",
            options: ["Madagascar", "Fuji", "Jamiaca", "Mexico"],
            correct: "Madagascar",
        },
        {
            id: "35",
            question: "What coloured vegetable is now mainly orange but can also be purple and yellow?",
            options: ["Banana", "Orange", "Carrots", "Pineapple"],
            correct: "Carrots",
        },
        {
            id: "36",
            question: "What is the main ingredient of bread?",
            options: ["Sugar", "Flour", "Egg", "Salt"],
            correct: "Flour",
        },
        {
            id: "37",
            question: "In general, roughly how many months does a human pregnancy last?",
            options: ["9 months", "7 months", "8 months", "10 months"],
            correct: "9 months",
        },
        {
            id: "38",
            question: "What is the largest mammal currently inhabiting the earth?",
            options: ["Shark", "Blue Whale", "Elephant", "Dragon"],
            correct: "Blue Whale",
        },
        {
            id: "39",
            question: " Often described as the longest river on earth, on which continent would you find the Nile?",
            options: ["America", "Asia", "Africa", "North America"],
            correct: "Africa",
        },
        {
            id: "40",
            question: "Deciduous trees lose their leaves at certain times of the year. What is the name of trees that don’t?",
            options: ["Coniferous or Evergreen", "Coniferous", "Evergreen", "None"],
            correct: "Coniferous or Evergreen",
        },
        {
            id: "41",
            question: "What is the largest land animal to roam the planet?",
            options: ["The Asian Elephant", "The American Elephant", "The European Elephant", "The African Elephant"],
            correct: "The African Elephant",
        },
        {
            id: "42",
            question: "What is the name of the rainforest that is synonymous with Brazil?",
            options: ["Amazon", "Zulu", "Brasile", "Coritiba"],
            correct: "Amazon",
        },
        {
            id: "43",
            question: "In which circle are you most likely to find Polar bears?",
            options: ["Arctic Circle", "Alantic", "Pacific", "Galaxy"],
            correct: "Arctic Circle",
        },
        {
            id: "44",
            question: "According to the famous saying, how many lives does a cat have?",
            options: ["8", "3", "5", "9"],
            correct: "9",
        },
        {
            id: "45",
            question: "What bird is famous for being pink?",
            options: ["Flamingo", "Parot", "Camelon Bird", "Junk Bird"],
            correct: "Flamingo",
        },
        {
            id: "46",
            question: "What elements make up water?",
            options: ["Air and Hydrogen", "Oxygen and Air", "Oxygen and Hydrogen", "Chlorine and Hydrogen"],
            correct: "Oxygen and Hydrogen",
        },
        {
            id: "47",
            question: "What double b is a common school equipment used for heating science experiments?",
            options: ["Bunsen Burner", "Buna Burner", "Best Burner", "B Burner"],
            correct: "Bunsen Burner",
        },
        {
            id: "48",
            question: "True or False: Venus is the closest planet to Earth?",
            options: ["None", "True", "False", "I dont Know"],
            correct: "True",
        },
        {
            id: "49",
            question: "The gaseous elements helium, neon, argon, krypton, xenon, and radon are better known as what?",
            options: ["The oil Gases", "The Metals", "The Noble Gases", "The Inert Gases"],
            correct: "The Noble Gases",
        },
        {
            id: "50",
            question: "What is the simple name for molten rock that erupts from a volcano?",
            options: ["Lava", "Fire", "Liquid Fire", "Algae"],
            correct: "Lava",
        },
        {
            id: "51",
            question: "Appropriately, what is the name of Saturn’s largest moon?",
            options: ["Tanus", "Titan", "Sitan", "Mitan"],
            correct: "Titan",
        },
        {
            id: "52",
            question: "Which scientist came up with the theory of E=MC2?",
            options: ["Newton", "Archimedes", "Albert Einstein", "Henry Ford"],
            correct: "Albert Einstein",
        },
        {
            id: "53",
            question: "What oath is taken by doctors and named after an Ancient Greek physician?",
            options: ["Nepocratic", "Euphoppocratic", "Hippocratic", "Dempocratic"],
            correct: "Hippocratic",
        },
        {
            id: "54",
            question: "Who was the first black president of the United States of America?",
            options: ["Martin Luther King", "Opra Winfred", "Malcom X", "Barak Obama"],
            correct: "Barak Obama",
        },
        {
            id: "55",
            question: "Who had an affair in the White House with Monica Lewinski?",
            options: ["Bill Clinton", "George Washington", "Joe Biden", "Donal Trump"],
            correct: "Bill Clinton",
        },
    ]
}